>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 在我们最后的行动中，我们会看到
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In our final exercise
of this unit, we're gonna look at and
使用类关键字的实践。
practice with the class keyword.
您将将名称空间对象重构为使用类系统。
You're going to be refactoring a namespace
object into using a class system.
所以如果您有一个具有此感知编码的名称空间模式，并且
So if you had a namespace pattern
with the this aware coding and
您希望改为使用类语法来尝试组织该代码，
you wanted to instead use the class
syntax to try to organize that code,
然后我们就会把它重构成这样的语法
then we're gonna be refactoring
it into that class syntax.
特别是这里，我们要利用这个级别的优势。
In particular, here, we're gonna
take advantage of the class extends.
所以有几个功能
So there are a couple of functions
在此名称空间的定义中不存在此感知。
within the definition of this
namespace that are not this aware.
他们没有理由特别说明
And there's no reason for
them to be specifically on
我们称之为研讨会的特定对象
this particular object that
we're calling workshop.
他们基本上是帮手。
They are essentially helpers.
所以我们要做的是有一个叫帮手的家长班。
So what we're gonna do is have
a parent class called helpers.
然后我们就会有一个孩子类来扩展帮手
And then, we're gonna have a child
class that extends helpers, and
那个孩子的课是被称为工作坊的
that child class is the one that's
gonna be called workshop, and
它会继承这些帮手
it will inherit those helpers.
那么换句话说，
So in other words,
它将通过继承来构成对这些帮手的访问权。
it will compose through inheritance
to have access to those helpers.
那些不需要装订的人，因为他们不知道这一点。
And those won't need to be this bound,
because they aren't this aware.
如果您查看 EX JS，您将注意到您有一个 namespaced 对象。
If you look at the EX JS, you'll notice
that you have a namespaced object.
所有方法都在前面引用了所有这些点引用。
All the methods with all the this
dot references in front of them.
还有一些地方你有一些不知道的功能，所以
And you do have some places where you have
functions that are not this aware, so
他们没有束缚
they're not bound.
但你还有其他的地方
But you have other places
where they are bound, and
您需要确保这些人员在您连接类系统时仍在工作。
you need to make sure that those are still
working once you wire up a class system.
所以这里的想法不是把所有这些东西都定义在一个物体上
So the idea here is instead of defining
all these things on an object,
你会把这些都定义为一类的方法
you're gonna be defining all of
these as methods in a class, and
然后将该类实例化并使用它。
then instantiating that class and
using it.
这就是运动在课堂上的实质。
So that's the substance
of the exercise on class.
我们会在几分钟后再谈这个方案
We'll be back in a few minutes
to talk through that solution.
一如既往如果你被困住了
As always, if you get stuck and
您需要提示，您可以在前点固定文件中检出该解决方案。
you need a hint, you can check out
the solution in the ex dot fixed file.
>> 扬声器 2: 所以它听起来像是要分解到这个感知物体上，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So it sounds like for
breaking down into this aware objects,
原因在于其大小和可读性，以及
the rationale is less about size and
readability and
关于你想要每个人的分离的问题
more about the separation of concerns
where you would want each, kind of-
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes.
>> 演讲者 2: 好的，酷。 你回到引导逻辑
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay, cool.
You going back to the guiding logic
其中一个对象开始和结束此组合。
of the structuring, where an object
begins and ends for this composition.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的。 >> 演讲者 2: 该代表团。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: This delegation.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我认为这完全是你选择还是选择
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think that's true
entirely separate of whether you choose or
选择类或选择模块或
you choose classes or
you choose modules or
选择其他组织模式。
you choose some other
organization pattern.
我觉得你应该问问
I think you should be asking
what logically fits together and
都是最小的碎片
try to have the smallest pieces.
我的意思是，我不一定总是喜欢单一的责任原则，
I mean, I don't necessarily always go to
like the single responsibility principle,
但那是一个合理的地方对吧
but that is a reasonable
place to head towards, right?
把它当作一个指导原则是合理的。
It's reasonable to think about
that as like a guiding principle.
如果这件事在做些不同的事情也许应该
That if this thing is doing a bunch
of different stuff, maybe that should
只是做了几件不同的事情
just be several different things
doing those different pieces.